ギュ
There is no wind with a bear,
while any other side left along the cross.
It seconded that even travel through a little Clintus Martin.
Suddenly the ride橋 went back into the glamour.
The silver light those
in a real world.
Now, I say day,
but I 지em it.
Opposed to under the skies,
I call the light that I am.
We won't die with theắm,
and we're taking over it.
We need to go on the Close Zoneeda,
We are glowing.
High five!
The End
It's chillier outside than I thought it would be.
It's official. The trains are still down.
If I had decided to brave it and walk home, I definitely would have caught a cold.
Thanks for letting me stay here.
I'm freaking out.
Which one did he buy?
Kitagawa.
So, want the first bath?
A bath?
That'd be awkward, wouldn't it?
Not at all. I'll be busy playing the rest of the game, so go ahead.
Yeah, okay.
Well, tonight, I don't intend to sleep.
This one. It looked awesome on me during the shoot. Genius shopping, Maureen. Let's do this.
Huh?
The bathroom's free. I'm done. So...
Got it. I'll head that way in a minute.
And I left some fresh clothes out for you.
I need to do laundry, so just throw your stuff in the washer. Mind hitting start for me?
Not at all.
I didn't mean for it to play out like this, but it feels like Gojo death had plans.
Why'd he get so determined all of a sudden?
I invited him to sleep here, but I wasn't trying to take it to this level. I'm totally unprepared.
I heard this urban legend about how if you keep a condom in your wallet, you'll get hella rich.
Here's where it's Gojo. Good luck. Good luck. Good luck.
Baby, we are prepared!
Our bath is like going to the spa. It's super relaxing in here.
Sleeping over is bad. But if I never actually go to sleep, this is nothing more than an extended hangout.
At the end of the day, perspective is everything.
Why choose this one? Isn't this hoodie important to you? It's Shizuku-tan.
Yeah, but it's cool.
Do you have anything else?
It's all I've got that's toasty and will fit.
That's unfortunate.
I'm starting to lose my composure again.
The clothes I wore today are in the wash, so there's nothing I can do.
It's fine. I just need to focus on beating the game.
Kitagawa.
Yeah? What's up?
You don't look very comfortable.
Uh, how weird. I really look that uncomfy?
Yes. This is her home after all. She should be comfy in the middle of the couch.
Gojo's acting like a totally different person. He's being more assertive than usual.
I'm chillin', but I guess I can scooch over a bit.
Alright.
Gojo's the one driving this train, so he should say something first, right?
I'm sure he will soon, but this just feels wrong.
We're skipping a ton of steps.
We need to go on an official date.
We need to hold hands.
We haven't even had our first kiss.
We're totally jumping the gun.
So, we're gonna do it all right now?
This is too much.
All the bases in one night!
Mother truck, that hurt.
Kitagawa.
Do you feel okay?
That sounded really painful.
Tell me where it hurts.
Gojo, he's so close.
Let me help!
Is something wrong?
Just slow down.
Please.
Now isn't a good time.
I just need a second or two to calm down.
Maybe I could have a snack first.
Uh, sure.
I'm so sorry.
Why?
Yum!
I was like hella nervous.
But I feel way better now that my belly is happy.
Nervous?
Act natural, Maureen.
Fake it till you make it, girl.
Not to be rude, but are these noodles an okay snack?
Your diet.
Yeah, they're great.
I got the locale version so I can feast.
Instant noodles hit different at night.
I guess I don't eat them very often.
You don't?
My dad loves movies.
He would watch super long movie marathons on weekends.
When he inevitably got hungry in the middle of the night,
he snuck a secret cup of instant noodley goodness.
The sound of boiling water always woke me up.
So I'd crash the party.
Later it was, the better they tasted.
Or maybe they tasted better because I had to fight my dad for them.
I love family stories like that.
I've been so good about my diet,
but I'm craving fried food like crazy.
I bet you are.
What?
I won't see.
I won't.
I agree.
I vlog instead of sleeping and getting laid off
my dad's inside.
I will have to st
my dad'sded skin.
Well that's strange she's never been harsh before this conversation feels off did I choose the wrong
option huh all my saves they don't exist anymore I can't go back
yeah
Oh, shit.
Hmm. It's morning. I practically slept till lunch.
Hang on! So nothing happened last night? Explain yourself! Huh? Were you out here all night?
Yeah.
But why? Huh?
The energy drinks he bought are totally normal?
So the reason you wanted to stay up all night was to beat the game?
Right. Turns out it's easier said than done.
What went wrong?
I guess I'm a pretty empathetic person at times. Since I wasn't focused on the costume, I was tuned into the story more than I usually am.
That was a mistake.
Yikes. Maybe some brekkie will make you feel better?
I don't know. Thank you, but the thought of eating right now makes me want to...
Okay...
So it was Mira the whole time. She made them disappear.
The truth is, none of the others existed in the first place.
She dreamt them up as a way to forget what happened with her real family.
We watched her create a new family in her head, but in reality she was lying in a hospital bed for the entirety of the game.
The more she lost her grip on what was real, the more incoherent the conversations became.
When I realized what it was she was trying to forget, the I don't want to remember message got even creepier.
The game forces you to see things through someone else's tortured psyche.
His reaction is still so fresh. Perfect!
Their personalities faded. It seemed all they could do was argue.
As the nights went on, eating with friends became eating her friends.
If she consumed them, they could become one.
Her new family would never leave her.
It was way too dark for me.
And the worst part was the title screen after you beat the game.
Oh, Grace! I love that they threw in one final jump scare!
It's perfection!
That adds up.
She had a blast exploring the abandoned hospital.
There.
That looks about right.
Much more natural.
Undoing it and redoing it was a good idea.
Wait, Shion!
I beg you, listen to me!
I refuse!
You disgust me!
Remove yourself from my sight!
You make us want to vomit!
I told you, Mirai!
Happiness doesn't last forever!
Come in.
It's just me.
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
Suzuka made plans for Saturday.
She, uh, wants our thoughts on the spot.
Alright.
Trouble is, I'm supposed to go shopping with Maureen right before we'd need to leave.
So I was kinda hoping that you could come with us.
That's fine.
Sister Mira's wig.
You went out of your way to style it for me?
Yes.
You've been busy communicating plans with Suzuka and the rest of the group.
Helping with your cosplay is the least I can do.
Oh.
Thanks so much.
You're the best.
Are you styling Sister Claire's wig next?
Can I watch you?
I can't move my arms with you sitting so close.
But you're welcome to watch.
I'm such an idiot.
I read into nothing and sent my hopes to the roof.
I even put on my purest, prettiest undies.
I need to find a cave.
Like ASAP.
And never come out.
All that over an energy drink.
It high-key scared the crap out of me.
But it meant taking things to the next level.
Being friends is great.
But I want more.
I need to suck it up and tell him.
I like you.
So, will you go out with me?
Not so bad.
Easy money, right?
Back then, I could say it no problem.
But he freaks at romantic stuff and shuts down questions about us.
He's terrified of people getting the wrong idea.
What if he really just thinks of me as a friend and nothing more?
If I tell him I like him, that's it.
There's no more in between.
I didn't know.
I enjoy spending time with you and making your outfits, but I thought that we were just friends.
Uh, I'm at a loss for words here.
I'm sorry.
Let me think it over.
Oh, today, huh?
I'm actually busy with...
Let's see...
Right.
I need to practice drawing faces, so please excuse me.
Today's busy, too.
Mickey D's calls, bro.
Gojo already went home.
My stupid imagination hurt my own feelings.
It's not a fart stretch.
He's avoided me like I was the freaking plague once before.
Aww.
Mari?
Why have you looked like literal death today?
I haven't eaten.
I'm too depressed to think about it.
That's no good.
So when you skipped lunch today, it wasn't because of your diet?
I need help.
Imagine there's someone you just consider a friend.
How would you respond if they asked you on a date?
Someone asked you out?
Let's go.
It's just hypothetical.
I'd say no.
I don't like them.
For real?
That's so brutal.
Imagine if Kensei asked you out.
Barf.
So you get my point.
I would reject him.
There's nothing else I could do.
Exactly.
He's not my type, and I don't think I'm his.
He would never want to go out with me, and that's A-OK.
You get it.
Guess I already did.
Just needed confirmation.
She's right.
Friends are friends.
I knew that.
It's Maureen!
Oh.
Oh no.
Kitagawa.
Hmm?
I think you should go.
Huh?
Oh, I didn't mean it that way.
You're frying mackerel?
I was.
I know you want fried food.
You mentioned craving it the other night.
I figured fried fish was healthy enough, but apparently it's still too heavy to eat at dinner time.
I've never gone on a diet before, so I didn't know about the timing aspect.
You got here before I could call you and explain my mistake.
Why can't I just spit it out?
Sorry.
You came all the way here, and now you have nothing to eat.
I have this.
It looks great.
Uh, are you sure?
I can call today my cheat day.
Cheat day?
Would you like me to remove the breading?
I'm planning to grill Grandpa's fish.
Uh-uh.
I want it like this.
The crunchy breading and the fluffy fish are like soulmates!
That's good, but eat your vegetables, too!
What are these killer flavors?
It's plum and shiso, so it doesn't need any sauce.
It's healthier.
You're becoming quite the chef, Wakuna.
You think so?
Certainly.
Oh yeah, yours has grated daikon in it, Grandpa.
Nutritious and delicious.
After watching Maureen eat hers, my stomach's telling me to taste-test the fried version.
Then you can have half.
Don't be stingy.
I couldn't prepare very much, so no leftovers tonight.
I'm sorry.
Well then...
Hey, Gojo.
Walk with me?
Just tonight?
Yeah, I don't mind.
Wait for me here.
I'll go grab a coat.
Uh-huh.
It's been getting dark so early lately.
Yeah.
I forgot to mention.
Murakami told me...
Kitagawa?
Hey, while we're here, there's something I'd like to tell you.
I, uh...
Can I come over again tomorrow?
Of course.
I'd like that.
I'll give you some money for the food.
Huh?
You don't need to.
You pay me way too generously for making your outfits.
I want it to be honest, but I couldn't even look him in the eye.
Until recently, I've been going with the flow.
I told myself, if it doesn't work out, it doesn't work out.
I'm a big girl and I'll be fine.
If it doesn't work out now, I'll be crushed.
Has it always been like this?
I'm so gross when I'm depressed.
What's a cute girl like you doing out so late by herself?
If you're bored, we could...
Die in a hole.
I'm being such a weenie.
I need to pull my head out of my butt and be myself.
I'm mentally exhausted right now.
And we have our group cosplay this week.
That's it.
After we wrap up the coffin cosplay, I'm gonna tell him.
I have no choice.
I have to.
I have to tell Gojo that I love him.
We'll be right back.
I know.
I have to tell you.
What a spirit.
Is it not?
interventions in the late.
Is it enough to me?
How about club Acho?
New, new, new
可愛い会話
トキメキ感じて
君からの変身まで
可愛い会話
胸も高鳴る
雨変わるよ
君と変わるよ
可愛い会話
次回予告